<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Blast Off!</string>
    <string name="languages_intro">Many countries are represented in the International Space Station. Click the buttons to learn new phrases you will use when you go up there!</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello</string>
    <string name="my_name_is">My name is</string>
    <string name="i_am_an_astronaut">I am an astronaut</string>
    <string name="country_are_you_from">What country are you from?</string>
    <string name="goodbye">Goodbye</string>
    <string name="english">english</string>
    <string name="french">French</string>
    <string name="spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="japanese">Japanese</string>
    <string name="german">German</string>
    <string name="russian">Russian</string>
    <string name="crew_assembly">Crew Assembly Training</string>
    <string name="base_station_walk">Base Station Walk</string>
    <string name="mission_control">Mission Control!</string>
    <string name="skills_crew">Skills Achieved: Astronauts will learn team work, communication, problem-solving, and coordination skills!</string>
    <string name="skills_base">Skills Achieved: Astronauts will gain endurance, strength, and mobility skills!</string>
    <string name="skills_mission">Skills Achieved: Astronauts will gain balance and spatial awareness skills!</string>
    <string name="supplies_needed">Supplies Needed:</string>
    <string name="instructions">Instructions:</string>
    <string name="training_text">Its time to train to become an astronaut! Astronauts are in top shape and you need to be too! Click the buttons to begin your training!</string>
    <string name="mercury">Mercury</string>
    <string name="venus">Venus</string>
    <string name="earth">Earth</string>
    <string name="mars">Mars</string>
    <string name="jupiter">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="saturn">Saturn</string>
    <string name="uranus">Uranus</string>
    <string name="neptune">Neptune</string>
    <string name="mercury_name">In astronomy mythology, Mercury was the Roman version of the Greek god Hermes. He was the messenger for the other gods, and for this reason Mercury is often depicted in pictures with winged sandals. In addition to delivering messages, he was also the protector of travelers and merchants.</string>
    <string name="rocket_name">Rocket</string>
    <string name="helmet_name">Space Helmet</string>
    <string name="space_suit_name">Space Suit</string>
    <string name="rocket_hint_titleName">How to build a Rocket</string>
    <string name="helmet_hint_titleName">How to build a Helmet</string>
    <string name="spaceSuit_hint_titleName">How to build a Space Suit</string>
    <string name="helmet_instructions">What you need:\nMedium size balloon\nNewspaper or white office paper (office paper eliminates the need to paint the helmet white)\nWallpaper glue (or flour and water: 1 part flour to 2 parts water)\nApplication brush\nWhite paint (if using newspaper)\nScissors and markers or paints for decals \nTray for glue mix \n\nStep 1\nBlow up your balloon and find a small bucket or plant pot to sit it in. Cut newspaper, or office paper into long strips. With the application brush, coat each paper strip with the glue one strip at a time and paste onto the balloon. Once you have one layer done, have your child add a light coat of the glue over the paper to add strength. Let dry 4 hours. Repeat 3 to 4 times (to create 4 to 5 layers).\n\nStep 2\nOnce the final layer is dry, pop the balloon and remove the balloon from the interior of the helmet. Popping the balloon is my youngest daughter\'s favorite part! You now have a solid shell for your Astronaut Paper Mache helmet. Cut the bottom of the helmet opening to fit your little astronaut\'s head. Then cut an opening for the face.\n\nSTEP 3\nDecorate any way your little astronaut desires. They might need a little help with this if you want it to look NASA authentic.\n\nStep4\nCreate small camera and microphone paper. Roll up 2 small paper and tape them together and glue it to the top side helmet. </string>
    <string name="rocket_instructions">Tools you will need: \nA large refrigerator box.\nMisc. tools (box cutter, tape measure, straight edge, pencil, jigsaw)\nColor Craft paper, some paints or aluminium foil\nImagination\n\nBegin by cutting and laying flat the box. My dimensions were based on the size of my box so you may have to make adjustments.\n\nUsing a straight edge, mark and cut out the top angles and tabs. Each panel is 2 feet wide because my box was 12 feet total.\n\nThe tabs are 5 inches long and 2 inches wide. The receiving side is 2 inches wide. I made the receiving slot cuts by just eyeing up the tab locations when I stood it up. Widen the slots a little bit to make it easier to insert the tabs.\n\nRun a blunt tool down the cardboard to help make the folds where you want them to be.\n\nUsing any circular object you like, trace and cut out any windows you would like.\nThe fins are about 2 feet high with one tab the same as above.\nPaint the outside any color you want. Be careful not to apply too much paint or the cardboard might warp. Using a sharpie, you can make a few rivets and other lines on the ship.\nThe door can use some packing or duct tape to keep it sturdy and support open and close.</string>
    <string name="space_suit_instructions">What you need: \nPlastic bottles \nSilver paint and brush\nScissors\nBoots\nPatches\nTin foil\nWire cable Flex White\n\nStep 1: \nUse the 2 bottles to make a space backpack, like those worn by real astronauts to breathe. Once clean and dry paint them with metallic grey paint and attach them using white tape. Add ribbons for straps that will stick with adhesive glue, once the paint has dried.\n\nStep 2: \nFor the spacesuit, you also have different alternatives:\nUse white clothes: Pants or stockings / tights / leggings and a sweatshirt or T-shirt.\nMake a fitted suit with white cloth; if you have a sewing machine and some sewing skills, you can do this at home with the help of patterns. If not, it will have to be ordered at a dressmaker.\nYou can also go for a plain white onesie or boilersuit.\n\nStep 3: \nUse the wire cabe flex organizer to connect the top of the bottle (space backpack) to the suits</string>
</resources>
